What was your reaction?
I was outraged.
It was incomprehensible to me.
It was unconscionable.
And I felt that I needed to do something and do something quickly.
I don't think I've witnessed anything of that nature in my entire career.
Really?
Cap.
Feels like Cap.
Yeah.
This this police officer in Memphis, this is Capacious.
You didn't see Derek Chauvin.
She didn't see the Rodney King tape.
We've seen this over and over and over and over and over again.
I don't even need to see the tape to know that the inhumanity that the police have consistently brought upon citizens is incessant.
And she can try and act like this is oh, so beyond.
But we all know that one is five black officers.
So they're going to they're going to drag it.
And two.
She knew these officers behave this way and she was neglectful.
And so she's trying to do this to try and cover her ass.
Rest in peace to Tyree.
dedicated to circumstances who they were to escape.
This.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
One.
Three.
Two.